const questions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Do you have any pet peeves?',
        answer: 'Cupboard doors left ajar drive me a little crazy.',
    }, 
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'What non-tech projects are you currently working on?',
        answer: 'I picked up embroidery a few years ago and I am currently trying to fill a (narrow) wall with finished embroidery hoops.  Next up is learning how to sew!',
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Favourite family tradition?',
        answer: 'A slice of cake for breakfast on your birthday.  We put candles on the rest of the cake that night after dinner, for everyone to enjoy.  I love it.',
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Would you rather have your dishes or clothes be magically clean?',
        answer: "Easy - dishes.  I actually don't mind putting away clothes, it makes me feel like I’m ‘restocking’ my closet.",
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Are you an early bird or a night owl?',
        answer: "I’m a night owl who has read 'The 5AM Club' and is trying to change her ways.",
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What’s one thing that can instantly make your day better?',
        answer: "A really good lunch and an iced coffee, or a laugh-so-hard-your-stomach-hurts can turn my day around in a snap.",
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Do you consider yourself an introvert or an extrovert?',
        answer: "Definitely an introvert.  I am quite fascinated by personality types - some traits that often come up for me are Observer, Researcher, Logistician.",
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What do you look for in a boss?',
        answer: "I look for someone I can learn a lot from, who I wouldn’t mind being stuck in the trenches with, but also a person that I can have a conversation with",
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'What are your hobbies?',
        answer: "I love to read – I usually rotate between fiction and self-development books.  I also enjoy a wide variety of crafting - I’m really fascinated by fibre arts, like embroidery and weaving.",
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: 'Do you have any travel plans?',
        answer: "Nothing booked, but some countries I'm hoping to travel to soon are: Denmark, Scotland and Austria. ",
    },
]



export default questions;